Wanchaloem Panyasen

Mobile: 089 998 0435

#### **Present position**

Senior Site Engineer/Supervisor C&S



#### Personal data

Last name Panyasen
First name Wanchaloem

Year of birth 1977 Nationality Thai

#### **Education**

2001 Bachelor of Civil Technology Engineer

Rajabhat Uttaradit Institute

#### **Key qualifications**

Experiences in a construction mostly with an industrial and power plant projects. Extensive experiences covering the scope of civil / structural and piping. Strong skill for controlling and supervising of Contractors during a project execution. Good experience of a New Greenfield Project starting from a land clearing, Temporary facility installation, Site Lay-out, Site setting, RC Piling, Structures installation, Architectural and Finishing, Quantity Control, Quality Inspection, Sampling and Testing and Handing over. Moreover with a clear view of project coordination with other disciplines such Mechanical and FFT, Electrical, Automation and Utilities. Positive mind with team working style.

## **Professional experience**

Jun 2013 – Aug 2019 Archetype Engineering Consultants Co., Ltd.

Position: Senior Site Engineer/Supervisor C&S Tebodin (Thailand) Co.,Ltd /BiLFINGER Thailand

Position: Civil Engineer

Project: QUECHEN SILICA (Thailand) - Q&C Thailand Project

- Brownfield Chemical

: CONTINENTAL REIFEN DEUTSCHLAND - APAC 2 Tires Project

- New Greenfield Chemical

: BASF CHEMCAT (THAILAND) - THEP Project

- New Greenfield Chemical

: NATIONAL STARTCH & CHEMICAL (INGREDION) - BKD Spitfire

- Brownfield Chemical

: LYONDELL BASELL - BAPT Expansion - Line # 5 Project

- Brownfield Chemical

# **Curriculum vitae**

#### Responsibilities:

- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor for project execution.
- Control and expedite the project schedule and working plan.
- Control a project time schedule / expediting plan
- Control a project quality / inspection and testing.
- Control a project budgeting.
- Control a project HSE.
- Coordinate all the site team among disciplines (CSA, ME, EE and Instrument / Control).
- Coordinate with operation team Designer and Contractor for an execution of work.

GLOW Co., Ltd.

Oct 2011 - July 2013

Position: Building Maintenance Officer.

#### Responsibilities:

- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor.
- Control quality / inspection and testing.
- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor for maintenance activity.
- Coordinate with operation team and Contractor.

#### **BUSINESS SERVICES ALLIANCE CO.,LTD (BSA)**

Jun 2010 - Oct 2011

Position: Technician.

#### Responsibilities:

- Control and supervise Sub- Contractor.
- Control quality / inspection and testing.
- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor for maintenance activity.

Jan 2008 - Jan 2010

#### PTT Maintenance and Engineering Co., Ltd.

**Position: Civil Inspector** 

**Project:** Assigned in a Project division for a Petrochemical plant.

Responsible for the project execution and maintenance work for a group of PTT where is rapidly grow and continue in expanding of its capacity.

### Responsibilities:

- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor for project execution.
- Control and expedite the project schedule and working plan.
- Control a project time schedule / expediting plan / catch up plan.
- Control a project quality / inspection and testing.
- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor for maintenance activity.

Aug 2003 - Dec 2007

Thai Copper Industry PLC.

Position: Foreman Civil

Responsibilities:

- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor.
- Control quality / inspection and testing.

# **Curriculum vitae**

- Control and supervise Sub-Contractor for maintenance activity.
- Coordinate with operation team and Contractor.

#### Language

	Speaking	Reading	Writing
English	2	2	2
Thai	1	1	1

Scale: 1. mother tongue | 2. Good | 3. working knowledge

# Computer skills

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point)

# Courses, certificates & award

- First aid and CPR training program.
- Basic Fire-Fighting
- Technical Fire-Fighting
- Safety Supervisor
- Scaffolding
- Kiken Yoshi Training (KYT)